# SHUBHAM KUMAR

#### Full Stack Web Developer

Passionate Web developer with good coding skills and love to contribute to the project and teamwork. Enjoying being at the Development Phase of my Career as a web developer. Build website all aspects of the user experience and user interface for the client. I am an ambitious and creative problem solver.



yuvraj.shubham.ss@gmail.com

Bengaluru,Karnataka, India

in linkedin.com/in/shubham-kumar-3a3b04163

8968119898

shubham00kumar.netlify.app/

github.com/shubham007kumar

# **EDUCATION**

### Full Stack Developer

Masai School

01/2021 - 07/2021

Bengaluru, Karnataka

# B.Tech(Computer Science and Engineering)

Lovely Professional University

06/2017 - 07/2021

Jalandhar, Punjab

# **Higher Secondary School** Lila Mandal S.S +2 School

22/22/14 22/22/5

03/2014 - 03/2016 Gaya,Bihar

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Frontend Developer

Salesken.ai

08/2021 - Present

Bengaluru,Karnataka

Providing CRM service to big company by analysis there call with customer and help there sales team improve performance.

# Hackathon

# Masai School

08/2021 - 08/2021

Bengaluru, Karnataka

This is the project that We developed during Hackathon. We are trying to build an examination portal for the CBSE students who are facing problems during pandemics.

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Tech stack used in this Project React JS, React-redux, Express.js and MongoDB
- Worked on Front end and chat bot for website

Contact: Avinash Kumar Sinha, Jagrati Panchal, Prashanth Vengala

#### Hackathon

### Lovely Professional University

08/2018 - 09/2018 Jalandhar, Punjab
Developed a website using React with the implementation of machine learning

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Object Detection using Tensor flow
- React
- Material UI

Contact: Yash Pathack

# **TECHNICAL SKILL**



# **PROJECTS**

#### Nykaa (06/2021)

- Developed Nykaa.com
- Beauty E-commerce website
- Tech stack used in this Project React JS, React-redux, and Firebase
- Worked on Front end and authentication of this website
- https://github.com/shubham007kumar/Deleted

#### INDIEGOGO (04/2021)

- Developed clone of indiegogo.com
- Fund Raising Website
- Tech stack used in this Project React JS, React-redux, and Styled-component
- collaborative project with 4 member
- Work on Routing of website and handling data from Heroku
- https://github.com/Bhargav1224/Nitrogen-IndieGogo

#### Himalaya (03/2021)

- Developed clone of Himalayausa.com
- Tech stack used in this Project HTML,CSS and JavaScript
- collaborative project with 4 member
- worked on product page ,cart page of website and static page of the website
- https://github.com/rao-kartik/team-damodar

#### **CERTIFICATES**

HackerRank (06/2021)

React Basic

MSHACKS (08/2018)

Hackathon

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Elementary Proficiency Elementary Proficiency

# **INTERESTS**

Cricket

Football

Video Editing